WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
— Good-bye, Sensei.
— Yay! School's out!
Good-bye, Iruka-sensei!
Good-bye!
Make sure you practice what
I taught you today, Transform Jutsu!
And tell your family about tomorrow's
inauguration for the Fifth Hokage!
— Okay!
— Okay.
Konohamaru!
What is it, Iruka-sensei?
Well... it's all right.
See you tomorrow!
Okay... Goodbye, Iruka-sensei!
It looks like he got over it.
Hey, Lee!
On your way back from rehabilitation?
Um... yes...
I hope you get better soon.
Thank you very much.
To activate each and
every cell all at once...
If it were just one by one,
it'd be a snap,
but all of them together
is gonna be tough.
Still...
The Leaf Village is
in great trouble right now,
so we must do our best!
I think if you had Tsunade-sama take
a look, you'd get better very quickly.
It's better that you give up being
a Shinobi and look for a different path.
The Bond Between the
Hot-Blooded Teacher
and
Pupil
When a Man Follows
His Ninja Way
~
Clone Jutsu!
Transformation Jutsu!
Hey, young kid...
The medal of youth is one of passion,
with no looking back!
If you work hard at it,
I'm telling you, son,
you will become a fine Shinobi! Yay!
Who is he?
He is pretty overbearing.
Son, be ambitious! Bloom of Youth...
Well then, adieu.
That was the first time I met Guy-sensei.
And then...
Today, you have all become Genin.
I want to hear what
your goals are for the future.
I don't want to answer.
I-I...!
I'd like to prove that
I could become a splendid Ninja,
even though I can't use
Ninjutsu or Genjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
Those are good serious eyes...
You! What's so funny?!
I'm serious!
I will become a respectable Ninja
even only with Taijutsu!
Don't you realize that
if you can't use Ninjutsu or Genjutsu,
you're not a Ninja in the first place?
Don't you remember being told
that you're the first person
to graduate from the academy
who's only able to use Taijutsu?
It's not because you're so good;
it's just that you're unusual.
W-Why...!
Listen up! If you have passion,
it's not necessarily so.
If you act with passion,
compete with good rivals
and lift each other up,
you can all become great Ninja!
But you know,
you have to work hard!
Passion...
I... was inspired by Guy-sensei.
By his words... and his deeds.
You're late!
17 minutes and 32 seconds late!
Let's not do it today, all right?
Each of us has 48 wins!
With a win today,
one of us will pull ahead!
I guess you won't give up
even if I say I wouldn't want to do it.
It's my turn to choose the event, right?
Right! What's it gonna be?
A Taijutsu battle? A 100-meter dash?
Holding our breath underwater?
I don't care, we could even
have an eating contest...
Please...
Okay, then...
Wh-What?!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors?
That's what you choose?
They say that your luck is
one part of your skill, don't they?
Plus, it's a great competition
for testing your observational reflexes...
R-Right.
Do you get the feeling
Kakashi's just playing around with Guy
'cuz he can't be bothered?
That's what it looks like to me.
I accept the battle.
There's no way I'm gonna lose!
If I do, I'll walk around the Leaf Village
500 times on my hands!
There you go again...
I promise!
Here we go...
Another one of your special,
self-imposed rules.
He can't do that.
That's ridiculous.
He's acting like a kid.
Yeah, that's impossible,
even for Guy-sensei.
Impossible? Reckless, I'd say!
— Rock, paper...!
Here you are.
Guy-sensei?
How did you know I was here?
I know everything about you.
I heard that you skipped out
on rehabilitation these past two days?
You can't be doing that!
When I first became Genin...
this is where I revealed
my dream, my aspiration.
Neji laughed at me then,
but I meant what I said.
I'd like to prove that
I could become a splendid Ninja
even though I can't use
Ninjutsu or Genjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
At that time, you told me...
If you act with passion,
compete with rivals,
you can become a fine Ninja.
And that...
In order to do that, it'd take "effort."
I was happy to hear that.
— Transform!
Because while at the academy...
no one, not one friend or teacher,
said that kind of thing to me.
You put me at ease...
You opened up a path
just when I was unsure of myself.
I realized all I had to do
was try my best.
And when I complained that
all my efforts couldn't match
the others' natural talents,
you told me that I had
a natural talent for effort.
That was when I learned the importance
of believing in my own strength.
The chance of a successful surgery
is probably 50%, at best.
But... this is one time...
even if I try my best...!
and even if I believe in myself,
there's nothing in the world I can do!
Guy-sensei... Please tell me...!
Please tell me.
Can I become like you?
Why did this kind of thing
happen only to me?
Because I have my own
Ninja Way to follow,
my own dreams and aspirations
that I have to protect and
prove to the world even
if it means dying for...
What should I do?!
The Eight Inner Gates...
Is this the Forbidden Jutsu that
will destroy the body of the practitioner?
Please tell me!
I'm prepared for the worst.
Please teach me that Forbidden Jutsu!
Everything is... for my dream!
That means everything to me!
You tried to become a great Ninja
relying only on Taijutsu...
Until now, that's all you had.
It must be so painful for you...
Now that it seems that your dreams
and all your wishes
are being cruelly taken away.
It does not matter what his wishes are,
he should give up on becoming a Shinobi.
Lee...
If you want to be free of that pain,
you have to prepare yourself!
Does it mean...
to prepare to give up my dreams?
If you lose your dreams,
you will undergo pain even greater
than what you feel now.
Neither you nor I would be able to
go on living if we lose the Ninja Way!
What fools we are...
Lee! Have the surgery!
How's it going with Cell Activation Jutsu?
It's all about the Chakra, but...
There are so many kinds of cells...
skin cells, internal organ cells,
muscular cells...
You know, it's just a tad difficult
to activate all of them at once.
What's that?
"Just a tad," you say?
Are you testing me?
Oh no!
I'm declaring my trust in you.
I don't know why,
but just a while ago...
I was remembering the time
when you and Kakashi-sensei
were competing
with rock, paper, scissors.
At that time, Kakashi-sensei said
that your luck is
one part of your skill, right?
This surgery is also fifty-fifty,
live or die...
But...
it's not a game of
rock, paper, scissors!
Do you remember what happened
after that, Lee?
500 times around...
It's a promise! Yay!
What's he doing?!
Crap!
If I lose, I'll walk 500 times
around the Leaf Village, on my hands!
It's a promise!
He can't do that! That's stupid.
He's acting like a kid.
Hah! This is nothing!
Wh-What are you doing here, Lee?
Why are you doing this?
Kakashi-sensei is not here.
In fact, no one is watching.
When a man stands cool with
a Nice-guy pose in front of others,
he should keep his promise,
even if it kills him!
It's a promise!
What?
Why do you always do that?
Whenever you're about to start
doing something,
why do you always come up
with some kind of crazy rule.
Good question, Lee.
You really know how
to get to the point.
Okay, I'll tell you.
But remember, you can't tell anyone else.
What's the answer?
Making self-rules is nothing less than
a practice which brings me victory!
S-Self-rules...?
Are you ready?
The point of these rules is that,
when you're going after something,
they push you into a real tough spot...
It's about chaining yourself down.
For example, on the other side
of the hellish rule that
"If I lose at rock, scissors, paper,
I'll do 500 laps" is the idea that
"If I do 500 laps,
there's no way I won't be able
to beat Kakashi next time."
They hold power,
the potential of the heavens.
Y-Yes...
By being chained down
to doing 500 laps,
it makes you get serious.
Even about things like
rock, paper, scissors competitions,
which are so trifling otherwise.
And, even if you lose,
walking around the village 500 times
gives you the benefit
of extremely intense training.
I see!
Okay, I've gotta do a little more.
Here we go!
I'm going with you!
I have my own "self-rule" which is...
Hey! Hey! Don't push yourself, Lee.
If I can't keep up with you, I'll...
try even harder!
That is, I'll aim to be like you.
And if I keep trying,
I'll be able to become a great Ninja!
All right! If that's the case,
then I have an addition to my rule!
If you can't keep up with me
all the way to the end...
I'll put every ounce of
my being into training you!
If I train you with all my being,
you'll be able to turn into a fine Ninja!
I promise!
Huh, that's right.
That was the first time you told me about
the "self-rule," wasn't it?
Your surgery will be a success
because you have worked hard
all the way through.
You have the power to bring
your own future in the heavens.
And in the one in a thousand...
no, one in a million chance
that something goes wrong...
I will die with you!
Ever since I met you,
my Ninja Way has been to
nurture you into a fine Ninja.
I promise you!
Neither you nor I would be able
to go on living if we lose the Ninja Way.
What fools we are...
G-Guy-sensei!
Okay, let's go, Lee!
Yes, sir!
Tsunade-sama!
From this day forward,
I am the ruler of the Village Hidden
in the Leaves, the Fifth Hokage!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
Damn! He has no hole
in his defense.
Being impatient won't
do any good, Naruto.
Let's utilize the next mission.
That's right. The next mission
requires an overnight stay.
— Our chance will be at the inn.
— Roger that!
Once we get to the inn,
we'll wait until he's defenseless...
— and then...
— unmask him at once!
Next time:
"I Want To See, I Want To Know, I Want To Check, Kakashi-sensei's Real Face!"
'Cuz we're really curious!